<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on </title>
    <link>/categories/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 23:25:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Gate and Let&#39;s Encrypt</title>
      <link>/2016/11/24/golden-gate-and-lets-encrypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 23:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/24/golden-gate-and-lets-encrypt/</guid>
      <description>I am currently serving all the things out of my home from behind my &amp;ldquo;Golden Gate proxy,&amp;rdquo; which is a combination of an nginx reverse proxy, an SSH WebSocket proxy, and an SSH bastion host.
My Golden Gate services are on their own dedicated VM, separate from the VMs running my actual services. I use the Certbot (previously Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt), &amp;ldquo;webroot&amp;rdquo; plugin which places some verification files at $DOMAIN/.well-known. However with a reverse proxy, there needs to be speical configuration section so that the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Perfect Browser</title>
      <link>/2015/05/19/my-perfect-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 20:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/19/my-perfect-browser/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to make everything I do online as secure as possible, while compromizing my expereince as little as possible. The most significant choice here is my web browser.
I rotate between a lot of them because none of the realistic options I&amp;rsquo;ve found meet all of my requirements.
Requirements:  Open source Tab sandboxing Supports Privacy Badger, uBlock, and HTTPS Everywhere (or equivalent feature set)  Preferred:  Automatic updates Cross platform (Windows, Mac, Linux, Android) U2F support LastPass support    FOSS Sandboxing Privacy Extensions   Chrome No Yes Yes   Chromium Yes Yes Yes   Firefox Yes No Yes   Opera No Unknown Not all   Safari No Yes No   Edge No Unknown No   So, Chromium meets my security requirements, but it&amp;rsquo;s unrealistic for a few reasons:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Measures: Servers and Data Storage</title>
      <link>/2014/12/30/security-measure-servers-and-data-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 04:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/12/30/security-measure-servers-and-data-storage/</guid>
      <description>This is a brief description of my security practices. I will make several posts and write updates as I make changes.
Servers I keep my data on a server running NAS4Free with one drive of parity. I also have servers running as VMs on a server running KVM and WebVirtMgr.
 On my NAS I only connect via encrypted methods such as AFP and SSH On my next upgrade, I will have my NAS encrypt on disk I only connect remotely to any of my servers/NAS via SSH or HTTPS  Photo Credit: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Measures: Client Devices</title>
      <link>/2014/12/30/security-measures-client-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 04:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/12/30/security-measures-client-devices/</guid>
      <description>This is a brief description of my security practices. I will make several posts and write updates as I make changes.
Client Devices The main security measure I take on my individual devices is to use full disk encryption and not allow anyone else to use the device (unless there is a guest account).
 On Macs I enable FileVault On Windows I use BitLocker On iOS I enable TouchID/password which encrpyts the device On Android I use the Encrypt Phone feature  I also install only necessary software, and do regular wipe and resintalls of the OS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Golden Gate</title>
      <link>/2014/12/23/goldengate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 21:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/12/23/goldengate/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is an outline for a project I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I&amp;rsquo;ll post updates as I progress.
Golden Gate aims to be a transparent reverse proxy that sits on the border of a network. It will handle all web requests coming into the newtork and pass them to the appropriate server. Except for Golden Gate, nothing will be open to the Internet in general.
Golden Gate aims to provide</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>